(INSECTS CHITTERING)
(WATER BURBLING)
(MAN YAWNS)
(LIVELY UPBEAT MUSIC)
♪ I WAKE UP EVERY EVENING ♪
♪ WITH A BIG SMILE ON MY FACE ♪
♪ AND IT NEVER
FEELS OUT OF PLACE ♪
♪ AND YOU'RE STILL
PROBABLY WORKING ♪
♪ AT A NINE-TO-FIVE PACE ♪
♪ I WONDER HOW BAD THAT TASTES ♪
♪ WHEN YOU SEE MY FACE ♪
♪ HOPE IT GIVES YOU HELL,
HOPE IT GIVES YOU HELL ♪
♪ WHEN YOU WALK MY WAY ♪
♪ HOPE IT GIVES YOU HELL,
HOPE IT GIVES YOU HELL ♪
♪ NOW, WHERE'S YOUR
PICKET FENCE, LOVE ♪
♪ AND WHERE'S THAT SHINY CAR ♪
♪ AND DID IT EVER GET YOU FAR ♪
♪ YOU NEVER SEEMED
SO TENSE, LOVE ♪
♪ I'VE NEVER SEEN
YOU FALL SO HARD ♪
♪ DO YOU KNOW WHERE YOU ARE ♪
♪ AND TRUTH BE
TOLD, I MISS YOU ♪
♪ I MISS YOU ♪
♪ AND TRUTH BE TOLD, I'M LYIN' ♪
♪ WHEN YOU SEE MY FACE ♪
♪ HOPE IT GIVES YOU HELL,
HOPE IT GIVES YOU HELL ♪
♪ WHEN YOU WALK MY WAY ♪
♪ HOPE IT GIVES YOU HELL,
HOPE IT GIVES YOU HELL ♪
♪ IF YOU FIND A MAN THAT'S WORTH
A DAMN AND TREATS YOU WELL ♪
♪ THEN HE'S A FOOL,
YOU'RE JUST AS WELL ♪
♪ HOPE IT GIVES YOU HELL ♪
♪ I HOPE IT GIVES YOU HELL ♪
(LIVELY UPBEAT MUSIC CONTINUES)
♪ TOMORROW YOU'LL BE
THINKING TO YOURSELF ♪
♪ YEAH, WHERE'D
IT ALL GO WRONG ♪
♪ BUT THE LIST GOES ON AND ON ♪
♪ AND TRUTH BE
TOLD, I MISS YOU ♪
♪ I MISS YOU ♪
♪ AND TRUTH BE TOLD, I'M LYIN' ♪
♪ WHEN YOU SEE MY FACE ♪
♪ HOPE IT GIVES YOU HELL,
HOPE IT GIVES YOU HELL ♪
♪ WHEN YOU WALK MY WAY ♪
♪ HOPE IT GIVES YOU HELL,
HOPE IT GIVES YOU HELL ♪
♪ IF YOU FIND A MAN THAT'S WORTH
A DAMN AND TREATS YOU WELL ♪
♪ THEN HE'S A FOOL,
YOU'RE JUST AS WELL ♪
♪ HOPE IT GIVES YOU HELL ♪
(GENTLE UPBEAT MUSIC)
♪ NOW, YOU'LL NEVER SEE ♪
♪ WHAT YOU'VE DONE TO ME ♪
♪ YOU CAN TAKE BACK
YOUR MEMORIES ♪
♪ THEY'RE NO GOOD TO ME ♪
♪ AND HERE'S ALL YOUR LIES ♪
♪ YOU CAN LOOK ME IN THE EYES ♪
♪ WITH THE SAD, SAD LOOK
THAT YOU WEAR SO WELL ♪
(LIVELY UPBEAT MUSIC)
♪ WHOO ♪
♪ WHEN YOU SEE MY FACE ♪
♪ HOPE IT GIVES YOU HELL,
HOPE IT GIVES YOU HELL ♪
♪ WHEN YOU WALK MY WAY ♪
♪ HOPE IT GIVES YOU HELL,
HOPE IT GIVES YOU HELL ♪
♪ IF YOU FIND A MAN THAT'S WORTH
A DAMN AND TREATS YOU WELL ♪
♪ THEN HE'S A FOOL,
YOU'RE JUST AS WELL ♪
♪ HOPE IT GIVES YOU HELL ♪
♪ WHEN YOU SEE MY FACE,
HOPE IT GIVES YOU HELL ♪
♪ HOPE IT GIVES YOU HELL ♪
♪ WHEN YOU WALK MY WAY,
HOPE IT GIVES YOU HELL ♪
♪ HOPE IT GIVES YOU HELL ♪
♪ WHEN YOU HEAR THIS
SONG AND YOU SING ALONG ♪
♪ BUT YOU NEVER TELL ♪
♪ YOU NEVER TELL ♪
♪ THEN YOU'RE THE FOOL,
I'M JUST AS WELL ♪
♪ HOPE IT GIVES YOU HELL ♪
♪ WHEN YOU HEAR THIS SONG ♪
♪ I HOPE THAT IT
WILL GIVE YOU HELL ♪
♪ HOPE IT GIVES YOU HELL ♪
♪ YOU CAN SING ALONG ♪
♪ I HOPE THAT IT PUTS
YOU THROUGH HELL ♪